https://www.sazerac.com/footer-pages/privacy-policy.html#CAPrivacyNotice

Privacy Policy
Last Updated: January 1, 2020
INTRODUCTION
This website and/or mobile application (collectively ”Site” or “Sites”) is provided by Sazerac Company, Inc., a Louisiana corporation and/or its affiliates (“Sazerac,” “we,” or “us”). Sazerac includes, without limitation, businesses operated under the following brand names: Click here to visit the brands page
The goal of this Privacy Policy is to inform you about the information we gather about you, how we use and share that information, and how we safeguard that information. This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect through any Site where this Privacy Policy is posted and information we collect offline, which we may combine with online data. Your use of this Site is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms of Use. By interacting with this Site, you consent to our collection and use of information as described in this Privacy Policy. By using this Site, you also certify that you are 21 years of age or above.
If you are under 21 years of age or do not accept this Privacy Policy in its entirety, please leave the Site immediately.
We may change or add to this Privacy Policy to the extent allowed by applicable law, so we encourage you to review it periodically. The top of this Privacy Policy identifies the date the Privacy Policy was last updated.
COLLECTION OF YOUR INFORMATION
Information You Provide to Us
We collect personal information from you when you interact with us via this Site. Personal information is information that identifies you or is reasonably linked to you. The personal information we may collect includes your name, email address, mailing address, shipping address, phone number, and/or credit or debit payment card information. Here are some examples of ways in which you may choose to interact with us:
Creating a personal account on our Site;
Making a purchase from us;
Enrolling and/or otherwise interacting with our customer engagement and loyalty programs;
Requesting customer service or otherwise contacting us;
Submitting a story, testimonial, rating or review, or other content to the Site for possible posting on the Site;
Participating in a contest, sweepstake, promotion, or survey;
Accessing Wi-Fi service we make available at locations or events we sponsor;
Opting in to a text message program; or
Otherwise submitting personal information to us.
Information from Other Sources
We also may collect information about you from third party sources. The information we collect from third party sources may include things like demographic information and purchase preference information. The third party sources may include public databases, social media platforms, data append services, data sharing cooperatives and others.
Automated Information Collection
We may receive and store certain types of technological information when you interact with our Site, our emails, and our online advertisements. This information is intended to help our Site work properly, to help us evaluate use of our Site, and to support our website analytics and marketing campaigns. Here are some examples of such information:
We may collect technical information like your internet protocol address, your device operating system and browser type, the address of a referring website, if any, and the path you take through pages you view on our Site.
We may use “cookies” to recognize you as you use or return to the Site. A cookie is a small text file that a website or email may save to your browser and store on your hard drive, computer, tablet or smartphone. This allows us to provide a continuous and more personalized shopping experience for you. You can find more information about cookies and how they work at www.allaboutcookies.org
We may also use web beacons (also called pixel tags or clear gifs). These web beacons allow us to know if a certain page was visited, an email was opened, or if ad banners on our Site and other sites were effective.
Certain browsers or browser add-ons, such as Adobe Flash, may provide additional local data storage mechanisms that are used in a manner similar to cookies, and some of the content include on our Site makes use of this local storage. For example, a Flash cookie is a data file placed on a device via the Adobe Flash plug-in that may be built into or downloaded by you onto your device. Flash cookies may be used for various purposes, including enabling a Flash feature and remembering your preferences. For more information about Flash and the privacy choices Adobe offers, visit: http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html.
We may also automatically collect information about your location when your mobile device is set to provide location information. For example, your device may allow us to show you the location of the retail store that offers Sazerac products that is closest to your location. We may also be able to recognize the location of your device in locations where we provide free WiFi access. Please see the “Your Choices” section of this Privacy Policy for more information.
Automated Information Collection by Third Parties
Sazerac may participate in interest-based advertising. In doing so, we may use third-party advertising companies to display ads tailored to your individual interests based on how you browse and shop online. We may allow third-party companies to collect certain information when you visit the Site. This information is used to serve ads for our products or services or for the products or services of other companies when you visit this Site or other websites. These companies may use information such as click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over, hardware/software information, cookie/session ID, and IP address, during your visits to this Site and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or a third party web beacon to collect this information.
We also use Google Analytics, which uses cookies and similar technologies to collect and analyze information about use of the Sites and report on activities and trends. This service may also collect information regarding the use of other websites, apps, and online services. You can learn about Google’s practices by going to google.com/policies/privacy/partners, and opt out of them by downloading the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, available at tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Please see the “Your Choices” section of this Privacy Policy for more information. If you are a California resident, please see our “California Privacy Notice” section below.
USE OF YOUR INFORMATION
Sazerac uses your information to offer and provide our products and services and to support our core business functions. These include order or service fulfillment, internal business processes, tailored promotional offers and rewards, marketing, authentication, loss and fraud prevention, public safety and legal functions. Here are some examples of the ways in which we use your information:
To respond to and fulfill your requests for products and services and communicate with you about those requests;
To register and service your account;
To administer surveys, sweepstakes, contests, and promotions;
To provide customer service and alert you to product information, including recalls;
To help us improve and customize our service offerings, websites, and advertising;
To send you information about our products, services, and promotions via various channels including email; and
To protect the security or integrity of our Sites and our business.
To accomplish these purposes, we may combine personal and non-personal information we collect with offline information, including information from third parties. We may transfer or disclose your information among our corporate affiliates.
We may also use information for any other purposes consistent with this Privacy Policy, as disclosed at the time you provide your information, or otherwise with your consent.
DISCLOSURE OF YOUR INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES
We do not rent or sell your personal information to third parties. We may disclose your personal information to third parties with your prior consent or under the following circumstances:
Service Providers:
Sazerac may share your personal information with service providers and other third parties who need access to your information to provide operational or other support services, such as direct mail vendors, shipping service providers, and other companies that help us improve our product and service offers and our Site. We require our service providers to keep your information secure. In addition, unless otherwise disclosed to you, our service providers are not authorized to use or disclose your personal information for their own marketing purposes.
Legal Requirements, Safety, and Loss Prevention:
Sazerac may disclose your personal information in other special circumstances. For example, we may provide personal information about you to regulatory authorities and law enforcement officials in accordance with applicable law, when we otherwise believe in good faith that the law requires it, or to respond to requests from government authorities. There may be instances when we may use or disclose your personal information in order to protect or defend the legal rights, property or operations of Sazerac or our employees or agents; to protect the rights, privacy, safety or security of users, members or others; to protect against fraud; and to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.
Business Transfers:
Sazerac may transfer any information we have about you in connection with a merger or sale (including transfers made as part of insolvency or bankruptcy proceedings) involving all or part of Sazerac or as part of a corporate reorganization or stock sale or other change in corporate control.
Aggregate Information with Third Parties:
We may share aggregate information (i.e., information that does not directly identify an individual) with third parties for lawful purposes.
YOUR CHOICES
If you would like to opt out of our promotional emails, please follow the unsubscribe link at the bottom of each such email.
If you would like to opt out of receiving direct mail from us, please do so by emailing info@sazerac.com. Please put OPT-OUT in the subject line and provide us your name and mailing address.
If you would like to change or delete your account information from the Site, please do so by emailing info@sazerac.com. Please put ACCOUNT INFORMATION in the subject line and provide us the website with your account information and instructions on the information that you want changed or deleted. Please note that, while we will do our best to address requests to change or delete your account information, we may be unable to delete all information associated with past communications or transactions.
Please be sure to include your full name, phone number, email address, the types of communications you would like to receive or not receive, and all relevant contact information in any communication you send to us. For example, if you would like to opt-out of receiving direct mail, please make sure to include your mailing address in your communication to us.
Please allow a reasonable time for your preferences to be processed. It may take up to 10 days to process your requests related to email and up to 30 days to process other requests.
Please be aware that, even if you opt out of receiving marketing communications from us, we may still contact you for transactional purposes such as customer service, product information, service notices, or recalls.
As explained above, Sazerac participates in online interest-based advertising. To learn more about online interest-based advertising, including how to opt out, visit the Network Advertising Initiative or the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising. Please note that the NAI opt-out mechanism relies on cookies to remember your choices with respect to ad-serving on websites. If you delete your cookies, use another computer or device, or change browsers, you will need to repeat the opt-out process. If you do opt-out of interest-based advertisements, you may still see advertisements on websites you visit, but those ads will not be based on your browsing behavior. If you are a California resident, please see our “Notice to California Residents” section below.
Some browsers have a “do not track” feature that lets you tell websites that you do not want to have your online activities tracked. This Site does not currently respond to such browser “do not track” signals, but we do provide you the option to opt out of online interest-based advertising via the NAI opt- out mechanism described above. To find out more about “Do Not Track”, please visit www.allaboutdnt.com.
Our mobile services may use location information transmitted by your mobile device. You can adjust the settings of your mobile device at any time to control whether your device communicates this location information. Please see your device instructions to learn more about these settings.
Other Privacy Rights. If you are a California resident, please see our “Notice to California Residents” section below for additional information about how to exercise your privacy rights. If you are a Nevada resident, please see our “Notice to Nevada Residents” section below for more information on additional rights you may have.
OUR COOKIES
Most web browsers allow you to exercise control over cookie files on your computer by erasing them, blocking them, or notifying you when such a file is stored. Please take a look at your particular browser for instructions on this function. You can choose to browse our Site without accepting our Site’s cookies. These cookies allow us to recognize you from page to page. Without these cookies enabled, you may not be able to take advantage of certain Site features.
INFORMATION SECURITY
Sazerac endeavors to maintain reasonable and appropriate physical, administrative, and technical controls to protect your personal information. While we work very hard to protect your privacy, no method of security is guaranteed to be effective, and we cannot be responsible for the actions of those who may gain unauthorized access to your personal information. We make no warranties, express, implied or otherwise, as to the ultimate effectiveness of our reasonable and appropriate safeguards. You are also responsible for taking reasonable steps to protect your personal information against unauthorized disclosure or misuse.
MOBILE APPLICATIONS AND SERVICES (INCLUDING WI-FI)
Sazerac’s mobile applications and services (including Wi-Fi service at events and/or locations we sponsor) may collect certain information automatically, such as the type of mobile device you use, the temporary or persistent unique device identifiers (UDIDs) placed by us or our service providers, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use, and information about the way you use our mobile applications and services.
Our mobile applications and services may also collect precise information about the location of your device through your device before our mobile applications and services obtain such location information from technologies like GPS, Wi-Fi, or cell tower proximity (or a combination of these technologies). Sazerac and our service providers may use and store this information, in combination with other location-based information such as IP address and billing or postal code provided by you at time of your mobile application registration, to provide enhanced location based services, such as search results and other content.
Users of our mobile applications and services may use the following mechanisms to opt-out of the collection and use of your precise location information:
You can stop all collection of information by our mobile applications by uninstalling the mobile application. You may use the standard uninstall processes available as part of your mobile device or via the mobile application marketplace or network. If you uninstall a mobile application from your device, the Sazerac unique identifier associated with your device may continue to be stored. If you re-install the application on the same device, Sazerac will be able to re-associate this identifier to your previous transactions.
You may at any time opt-out from further allowing us to have access to your location data by adjusting the permissions on your mobile device.
INTERNATIONAL
This Site is controlled and operated by us from the United States and is not intended to subject us to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country or territory other than that of the United States. Your personal information may be stored and processed in the United States or any other country in which Sazerac or its service providers maintain facilities. By using this Site, you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside of your country of residence, including the United States, which may have different data protection rules than in your country.
INDIVIDUALS UNDER 21 YEARS OF AGE
This Site is intended only for adults who are at least 21 years of age, and does not knowingly collect information online from anyone who is under the age of 21. Please contact us via the instructions provided in the Privacy Contact section of this Privacy Policy if you believe this Site has collected information from anyone who is under 21 years of age.
PRIVACY CONTACT
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or how your personal information is handled, please contact us by sending a letter to:
Sazerac Company
Attn: Compliance Department
10101 Linn Station Road, Suite 400
Louisville, KY 40223
You may also contact us by email through the Contact Us link info@sazerac.com on our Site.
NOTICE TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS
CALIFORNIA PRIVACY NOTICE
This California Privacy Notice is effective as of January 1, 2020.
This notice supplements Sazerac’s privacy policy and applies only to California residents. This California Privacy Notice sets forth disclosures and rights for California consumers regarding their personal information, as required by the California Consumer Privacy Act (“CCPA”). Terms used in this California Privacy Notice have the same meanings given in the CCPA and the regulations of the Attorney General implementing the CCPA, unless otherwise defined.
This notice provides information about the categories of information that we collect from California residents generally, the sources of the information, the purposes for which we use the information, and the categories of third parties to whom we disclose the information for business purposes and to whom we sell Personal Information as defined by CCPA (and information on how to opt-out).
INFORMATION SAZERAC COLLECTS
Sazerac collects information that identifies, relates to, describes, references, is capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with a particular consumer or device (”Personal Information”).
The following are the categories of Personal Information that we have collected from our users over the last 12 months, the categories of sources from which that information was collected, the business or commercial purpose(s) for which the information was collected, the categories of third parties with whom we disclose the information for a business purpose, and the categories of third parties to whom this type of personal information is sold.
The Personal Information we collect about you will depend upon how you use our Sites or otherwise interact with us. Accordingly, we may not collect all of the below information about you. We may also collect and/or use additional types of information after providing notice to you before collection and obtaining your consent (to the extent such notice and consent is required by the CCPA).
Category of Personal Information Collected
Business or Commercial Purpose(s) for which Information is Collected
Categories of Sources from which the Information was Collected
Categories of Third Parties to whom this type of Personal Information is Disclosed for a Business Purpose
Categories of Third Parties to Whom this Type of Personal Information is Sold
Identifiers
This category includes information such as name, contact information, and online or device identifiers.
We may collect this type of information from:
Consumer,
Cookies and Tracking Technologies,
Third Party Service Providers,
Third Party Social Media Companies,
Third party Business Partners,
Third Party Data Resellers.
We may use this type of information:
To respond to and fulfill your requests for products and services and communicate with you about those requests;
To register and service your account;
To administer surveys, sweepstakes, contests, and promotions;
To provide customer service and alert you to product information, including recalls;
To help us improve and customize our service offerings, websites, and advertising;
To send you information about our products, services, and promotions via various channels including email; and
To protect the security or integrity of our Sites and our business.
We may disclose this type of information to:
Service Providers, such as third parties who help manage our websites and deliver our communications,
Third parties we partner with for contests, sweepstakes, or promotions,
Third party advertising and analytics companies,
Third parties who may acquire your information as a result of a merger, acquisition or other ownership transition,
Third parties or affiliated companies when you agree to or request that we share your information with them,
Other third parties (including government agencies) as required by law (such as pursuant to subpoenas or court orders).
Third party advertising business partners may have access to this data, and this may be considered a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances.
Any categories of personal information described in subdivision (e) of Section 1798.80
This category includes name, address, and phone number, information about your employment or education, and other categories of information classified as “personal” under this California law.
We may collect this type of information from:
Consumer,
Cookies and Tracking Technologies,
Third Party Service Providers,
Third party Social Media Companies,
Third Party Business Partners,
Third Party Data Resellers.
We may use this type of information:
To respond to and fulfill your requests for products and services and communicate with you about those requests;
To register and service your account;
To administer surveys, sweepstakes, contests, and promotions;
To provide customer service and alert you to product information, including recalls;
To help us improve and customize our service offerings, websites, and advertising;
To send you information about our products, services, and promotions via various channels including email; and
To protect the security or integrity of our Sites and our business.
We may disclose this type of information to:
Service Providers,
Service Providers, such as third parties who help manage our websites and who deliver our communications,
Third parties we partner with for contests, sweepstakes, or promotions,
Third party advertising and analytics companies,
Third parties who may acquire your information as a result of a merger, acquisition or other ownership transition,
Third parties or affiliated companies when you agree to or request that we share your information with them,
Other third parties (including government agencies) as required by law (such as pursuant to subpoenas or court orders).
Third party advertising business partners may have access to this data, and this may be considered a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances.
Commercial information
This category includes, for example, payment information you provide for goods, services, customer service records, and information about the products you have purchased
We may collect this type of information from:
Consumer,
Third Party Service Providers,
Third Party Business Partners.
We may use this type of information:
To respond to and fulfill your requests for products and services;
To administer surveys, sweepstakes, contests, and promotions;
To provide customer service;
To help us improve and customize our service offerings, websites, and advertising; and
To protect the security or integrity of our Sites and our business.
We may disclose this type of information to:
Service Providers, such as third parties who help manage our websites,
Third parties we partner with for contests, sweepstakes, or promotions,
Third party advertising and analytics companies,
Third parties who may acquire your information as a result of a merger, acquisition or other ownership transition,
Third parties or affiliated companies when you agree to or request that we share your information with them,
Other third parties (including government agencies) as required by law (such as pursuant to subpoenas or court orders).
Internet or other electronic network activity information
This category includes information about the web browser and operating system you are using, the website or ad that referred you to our Sites, areas of the Sites that you visited, and terms entered into a search engine that led you to the Sites.
We may collect this type of information from:
Consumer,
Cookies and Tracking Technologies,
Third Party Service Providers,
Third Party Business Partners,
Third Party Data Resellers.
We may use this type of information for:
To respond to and fulfill your requests for products and services;
To provide customer service;
To help us improve and customize our service offerings, websites, and advertising; and
To protect the security or integrity of our Sites and our business.
We may disclose this type of information to:
Service Providers, such as third parties who help manage our websites,
Third party advertising and analytics companies,
Third parties who may acquire your information as a result of a merger, acquisition or other ownership transition,
Third parties or affiliated companies when you agree to or request that we share your information with them,
Other third parties (including government agencies) as required by law (such as pursuant to subpoenas or court orders).
Third party advertising business partners may have access to this data, and this may be considered a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances.
Inferences drawn from any of the information identified above to create a profile about a consumer
These inferences may relate to your perceived interests, preferences, characteristics, or behavior.
We may collect this type of information from:
Consumer,
Cookies and Tracking Technologies,
Third Party Service Providers,
Third party Social Media Companies,
Third Party Business Partners,
Third Party Data Resellers.
We may use this type of information:
To help us improve and customize our service offerings, websites, and advertising.
We may disclose this type of information to:
Service Providers,
Third parties we partner with for contests, sweepstakes, or promotions,
Third party advertising and analytics companies,
Third parties who may acquire your information as a result of a merger, acquisition or other ownership transition,
Third parties or affiliated companies when you agree to or request that we share your information with them.
Third party advertising business partners may have access to this data, and this may be considered a sale under CCPA under certain circumstances.
EXERCISING YOUR CALIFORNIA ACCESS, DELETION, AND DO-NOT-SELL RIGHTS
You have the right to request that we disclose to you what Personal Information we collect, use, disclose, and sell, including the right to request that we provide to you the specific pieces of Personal Information we have collected about you in the prior 12 months (“Right to Know”) and you have the right to ask us to delete the Personal Information we collect about you (“Right to Delete”), subject to exceptions set forth in the CCPA. California residents also have the right to opt-out from the sale of their Personal Information. These rights are subject to some limitations, such as when we are retaining data to comply with our own legal obligations. You will not be required to create an account with us in order to submit a request. More information on each of these rights is below.
If you would like to authorize an agent to act on your behalf in submitting a request to know, request to delete, or request to opt-out of the sale of your Personal Information, you may do so by sending an email indicating the name of your authorized agent to CCPARequests@Sazerac.com. Please keep in mind that if we do not receive adequate proof that the agent is authorized to act on your behalf, we may deny the request. Response Timing When you request access to the Personal Information we have collected or deletion of your Personal Information, we will typically provide the requested information within 45 days, and we will notify you within that time period if we need additional time to process your request. When you opt-out from the sale of your Personal Information, we will honor your request as soon as feasible, but no later than 15 days from the date we receive your request.
RIGHT TO KNOW
1. Making A Request
If you are a California resident and would like to request information about the Personal Information we have collected about you in the prior 12 months, please contact us at this email address: CCPARequests@Sazerac.com and provide your first and last name, state the nature of your request, and include your phone number and email address, which we will use to verify your request as described below. You may also call us toll-free at 1-866-729-3722.
We will provide the requested information free of charge up to two (2) times in a 12-month period, but please note that where we receive unfounded, excessive, or repetitive requests, we may elect to decline the request. Note also that we will not be able to provide information we do not ordinarily retain in the course of our regular business practices.
2. Verifying Requests to Access
Please note that we will take steps to verify your identity in order to fulfill your request.
In order to verify your identity, we will request that you provide the following pieces of information when you email us with your request: your first and last name and the phone number and email address that you have previously provided to Sazerac.
In order to have us provide specific pieces of information, we may require a signed declaration under penalty of perjury that you are the consumer whose Personal Information is the subject of the request.
If we are unable to verify that the individual submitting the request is the same individual about whom we have collected information (or someone authorized by that individual to act on their behalf), we will not be able to provide the requested information.
RIGHT TO DELETE
The CCPA also provides a right to request that we delete personal information we have collected about you and for us to direct service providers to do the same, with certain exceptions as set forth in the CCPA.
When processing a request to delete, we may erase some information and we may de-identify some information (when we de-identify information, we implement technical safeguards and business processes that prohibit re-identification, business processes to prevent inadvertent release of de-identified information, and will make no attempt to re-identify the information).
1. Making A Request
If you are a California resident and would like to request that we delete your information, please contact us at this email address CCPARequests@sazerac.com and provide your first and last name, state the nature of your request, and include your phone number and email address, which we will use to verify your request as described below. You may also call us toll-free at 1-866-729-3722.
2. Verifying Requests to Delete
To ensure that we do not delete your personal information in response to a fraudulent request, once you submit the request, we will follow up to confirm that you want your information to be deleted.
In order to verify your identity, we will request that you provide the following pieces of information when you email us with your request: your first and last name and the phone number and email address that you have previously provided to Sazerac.
If we are unable to verify that the individual submitting the request is the same individual about whom we have collected information (or someone authorized by that individual to act on their behalf) we will not delete the information but we will process the request as a “Do Not Sell” request.
RIGHT TO OPT-OUT OF THE SALE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION
The CCPA also provides a right to California residents to request to opt-out of the sale of Personal Information. As indicated above, we may allow third-party advertising companies to collect data from visitors to our Sites, including to better serve you more relevant advertisements. This may potentially be considered “sales” under the CCPA under certain circumstances.
Some of the companies we work with for analytics and advertising purposes are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“NAI”) or the Digital Advertising Alliance (“DAA”) Self-Regulatory Program for Online Behavioral Advertising and you may want to visit the following webpages, which provide information regarding procedures for opting out of targeted online advertising and “opt-out” mechanisms for participating companies: http://networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp and http://www.aboutads.info/choices/. For information about the DAA’s AppChoices application, click here.You may opt-out from interest based advertising on your mobile device through your mobile device settings.
You may also be able to limit the access these third-party advertising companies have to information about you when you use our Sites by installing a browser or browser extension that can enable you to block the functionality of some tracking technologies.
If you use different computers or browsers, you may need to indicate your opt-out choices across those computers and browsers.
Users Younger than 16
Sazerac does not knowingly collect or sell Personal Information of minors younger than 16 years of age without affirmative authorization.
Right to Non-Discrimination for the Exercise of a Consumer’s Privacy Rights
California consumers have the right to not receive discriminatory treatment for exercising CCPA rights. We will not discriminate against you for exercising your CCPA rights. Contact for More Information You can contact us for more information by writing us at Sazerac Company, Attn: Compliance Department, 10101 Linn Station Rd., Suite 400, Louisville, Kentucky 40223 or emailing CCPARequests@Sazerac.com.
Other California Rights/YOUR CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS
Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, residents of the State of California who provide us personal information have the right to request and obtain from us one time per calendar year information about the customer information we shared, if any, with third parties for their own direct marketing purposes during the preceding year. If applicable, this information would include the categories of customer information and the names and addresses of those businesses with which we shared customer information for the immediately preceding calendar year.
If you are a California resident and Sazerac customer, you can request a notice disclosing the categories of information we have shared with third parties for the third parties’ direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year. This information will be provided in a standardized format and will not be specific to you individually. To make such a request, please send a letter to the following address:
Sazerac Company
Attn: California Shine the Light Request
10101 Linn Station Road, Suite 400
Louisville, KY 40223
You must include the statement “Your California Privacy Rights” on your letter. You must include your name, street address, city, state, and zip code. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information.
NOTICE TO NEVADA RESIDENTS
Sazerac does not currently sell your covered information as those terms are defined under applicable Nevada law. However, you may still submit an opt-out request and we will honor that request as required by Nevada law if Sazerac were to ever engage in such a sale in the future. If you are a Nevada resident and would like to opt-out of future sales of your covered information, please submit your request to 1-866-729-3722. Your request must include your full name, street address, city, state, zip code, and an email address so that we can contact if needed regarding this request. You may also be required to take reasonable steps as we determine from time to time in order to verify your identity and/or the authenticity of the request. Sazerac will respond to your request within sixty (60) days either confirming that your request has been processed or indicating that we need an additional thirty (30) days to complete the request.
SAZERAC COMPANY, INC.
